听着 我知道这不是最好的感恩节之一
Look, I know it wasn't the best Thanksgiving,
但是尼克会没事的
but Nico is going to be fine.
是的 他是我的小宝贝
Yeah, he's my baby boy.
他都21岁了 爸
He's 21, Dad.
是啊 但是他挺敏感的
Yeah, but he's sensitive.
他不够坚强也没你那么体魄健壮
He's not tough and brawny like you.
-健壮？-听着 别担心我
- Brawny? - Look, don't worry about me
也别担心家里了
or this family.
你去好好玩 努力学习
You go have fun, study hard,
找个男朋友...
find a boyfriend...
像其他年轻人一样
Be young.
好吧 爱你
Okay. I love you.
你确定你现在的状态开车没事吗？
Are you sure you're good to drive?
我不确定 开开看吧
I don't know, we'll see.
我觉得可以的
I think so.
再见 宝贝
Goodbye, pumpkin.
这呢 拿着你的包
Here, hold your bag.
-我没事 卡罗尔 -好吧
- I'm fine, Carol. - All right.
哦天哪 惠特尼 你好啊
Oh, my God, Whitney, hi!
你感恩节过得怎么样？挺好的
How was your Thanksgiving? Really good.
等会儿 你们从亚利桑那州开车回这里的吗？
Wait, did you guys drive here from Arizona?
这路不是挺远的吗？
Isn't that a long trip?
是啊 39个小时呢 实际感觉起来更长
Yeah, it's 39 hours, and it felt like a lot more.
是啊 结果就是花了1500刀在加油和住宿上
Yup, it ended up costing $1,500 in gas and hotels.
我们还让一对夫妻狠狠吵了一架
And we got in a couple really bad arguments.
啊 那也改不了路途遥远的事实
Ah, wouldn't change a thing.
你好啊 嘿！
Hi! Hey.
哦 我的天哪 你家里怎么样
Oh, my goodness. How's your family?
-嗯 挺好的 我们领养了只狗 -噢
- Uh, good. We adopted a dog. - Ooh.
我妈觉得这有助于她的支持率
My mom thought it would help her approval ratings.
事实上没有 然后就把小狗退回去了
It did not. She returned it.
她真是个不得了的女人啊
She is an amazing woman.
我总在我朋友那替她说好话
I always defend her to my buddies.
-爸！-好吧 亲爱的
- Dad! - Well, honey,
我们得走了 我明天还得上班呢
we should head out. I gotta work in the morning.
-回亚利桑那州上班？-对啊
- In Arizona? - Yeah.
我们尽量路上不停下来了
We're gonna try not to stop.
-再见 亲爱的 -好的 再见
- Bye, sweetie. - Okay, bye.
-我们爱你哟 -开车注意安全
- We love you. - Drive safe.
-爱你 -我爱你 亲爱的
- Love you. - I love you, pinochle.
坐了这么久的车 我现在就想好好休息一下
After that long drive, I just really wanna relax.
是啊
Yeah.
惠特尼！金伯莉！
Whitney! Kimberly!
我想死你们几个了 快过来！
I missed you bitches. Come here!
-嘿 -嘿 贝拉
- Hey.- Hey, Bela.
诶 对不起
Uh, sorry,
你的衣服呢
where are your clothes?
我十五分钟前到这儿的
Got in about 15 minutes ago,
让自己舒服点 给自己弄了点小零食
got comfortable, made myself some snacks.
在家里我爸妈执着于
My parents were, like, obsessed with me
让我穿衣服 -噢 我同意你爸妈的
wearing clothes at home. - Oh, totally.
你坐上沙发前
Would you mind putting a towel down
能不能铺个毛巾毯
before you sit on the sofa?
-为什么？-因为你屁股光着
- Why?- Because of your butt.
-蕾登 嘿！-欢迎回来！
- Leighton, hey! - Welcome back!
-嘿！-大家好啊
- Hey! - Hi, all.
我有个事情要宣布
I have an announcement.
你怎么穿着内衣
Why are you in your underwear?
这样舒服
For comfort.
哦 好吧 尼克被开除了
Okay, well, Nico got expelled.
-什么？ -噢 我的天哪
- What? - Oh, my God.
-你是说真的？-对啊
- Are you serious? - Yeah.
金伯莉把偷来的考试文件上交的时候
When Kimberly turned in the stolen test files,
教务处就开始了一些列的调查
the administration started an investigation,
Theta兄弟会的一些高年级的成员被踢出去了
and a bunch of senior Thetas got kicked out.
高年级的？可是他们是最帅的一批人诶
The seniors? But they were the hottest ones.
那尼克打算怎么办
What's Nico gonna do?
这个嘛 谢天谢地 我爸能给康奈尔
Well, thankfully, my dad was able to make
捐一大笔钱 下学期给他在学校找个位置塞进去
a big donation to Cornell and got him a spot next semester.
而且他们为了让他高兴给他买了辆奥迪
And they got him an Audi to try and cheer him up.
行吧 这个故事一下子就没那么惨了
Mm-kay, this story is getting less sympathetic.
真是遗憾 你哥哥这么老帅
I'm so sorry. Your brother was gorgeous,
我会怀念在校园里看见他的脸和身材的日子
and I'm gonna miss seeing his face and body around campus.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你穿的是我的内衣吗？
Are you wearing my underwear?
就内衣啦...噢内裤也是你的！
Just the bra... oh! Bottoms too.
-金伯莉 -嗯？
- Kimberly. - Yeah?
你告诉你爸妈你的奖学金没了吗
Did you tell your parents about losing your scholarship?
噢 我还没找到合适的时机告诉他们
Oh, I couldn't find the right time to mention it to them.
什么意思？你跟他们待在车上39个小时诶
What do you mean? You were in the car for 39 hours.
就是啊 你不是需要很多很多的钱吗？
Yeah, don't you need, like, a lot of money?
噢 就每年42000刀啦...
Oh, just $42,000 per year...
加起来138000刀
$138,000 total.
真的假的？那可是 大概 四辆车了
Seriously? That's, like, four cars,
或者 大概 蕾登五个包的钱
or, like, five of Leighton's purses.
姐妹 我觉得你应该告诉你爸妈的
Dude, I think you need to tell your parents.
我开不了口 这比杀了他们还难受
I can't. It would kill them.
我得自己想个招
I need to figure out a solution on my own.
招儿来了
Solution's right here.
问这俩有钱人要点
Ask one of these two moneybags for it.
他们的父母很有钱
Their parents are loaded. Uh...
我是说 别指望我
I mean, don't look at me.
蕾登的家庭比我的有钱多了
Leighton's family's way richer than mine is.
我家是从政的有钱
We're politician rich.
那个 我家大部分的财富都跟
Well, most of my family's wealth is tied up
一些土地和赛马绑定在一起了
in real estate and, um, several racehorses.
噢 你俩不需要让你们的
Oh, you guys don't need
有钱家庭听起来很穷的样子
to make your rich families sound poor.
我不会要你们任何一个人的钱的
I would never ask either of you for money.
我自己走到这个境地的 我会把自己救出来的
I got myself into this, and I'll get myself out.
等等 我知道了 如果你需要额外的钱
Wait, I've got it. If you need extra money,
你可以去按网上卖一些玉足照片
you should sell feet pics on the dark web.
这真的是
That's certainly
一个有趣的主意 -金伯莉 不要
an interesting idea. - Kimberly, no.
你就去助学金办公室申请贷款
Just go to the financial aid office and apply for a loan.
别啊 我的计划更好 你脚指头很长
No! My plan is better. You've got long toes,
是真的有这方面的需求市场
and there's a real market for that.
-别说了！-贝拉！
- Stop! - Bela!
怎么了嘛？不要觉得我的好主意
What? Don't shame me
丢人啊
for my good ideas.
姐妹们 我们一直在说这个学校需要什么？
Guys, what are we always saying this campus needs?
-更好的Wi-Fi？-一个染眉毛
- Better Wi-Fi? - A decent place
的好去处？
to get my eyebrows tinted?
一个原住民的纪念碑
A memorial to Native peoples.
不是
No.
一本全女性的喜剧杂志
An all-female comedy magazine.
我跟一些朋友
I'm starting one
正在合办一本
with some friends.
我们一次性推翻一个
We're toppling the patriarchy
排名前十的男权问题
one top-ten list at a time.
杂志 嗯 还在流行吗？
Are magazines, like, a thing anymore?
这个嘛 至少我们的杂志可以成为Instagram上的新风尚
Well, ours would mostly be an Instagram presence,
Twitter上的时髦话题 以及一个
a sassy Twitter account, and a website
由我们主导的新兴领域网站
that we haven't bought the domain for yet.
这会是个大事的 多酷啊
It's gonna be huge. That's so cool.
-是的 -贝拉 我不得不说
- Yeah. - Bela, I have to say,
目前来看 我支持你
so far, I support this.
对吧
Yeah.
-他爹的怎么回事儿？-噢 我的天哪 你还好吗？
- What the fuck? - Oh, my God, are you okay?
是谁用牛奶盒砸我啊？
Did somebody just hit me with a milk carton?
噢 天哪 你刚刚被击中了
Oh, man. You just got nailed.
是啊 这也太糟糕了
Yeah, that was so fucked up.
-就是啊 可不么 -这一定很让你
- Yeah, I know. - That must have been
意外吧
really surprising.
嗯 对啊 当然了
Um, yeah, it was.
所以即使你什么都没做错
So even though you didn't do anything wrong,
坏事还是会找上门？
something bad still happened to you?
你干嘛这样说话？
Why are you talking like that?
就是啊 听起来跟个寓言故事的开头一样
Yeah, it sounds like the beginning of a parable.
因为我们他爹的在Theta兄弟会
'Cause we're in fucking Theta,
你们几个人让我们的特许状被暂停使用了
and you guys got our charter suspended.
等等 这就是原因？
Wait, is that what this is about,
考试那件傻事儿？
the stupid test thing?
对 你们抓住我们了 你们这些警察
Yeah, you narced on us, you narcs.
就因为你们的愚蠢行为 我们可惨了
That stunt you pulled fucked us.
我们再也不能办派对了
We can't throw parties anymore.
所以你就他爹的朝我扔牛奶？
So you threw a fucking milk at me?
-这件毛衣800刀呢！-什么？
- This sweater cost $800! - What?
是你们这些蠢货考试作弊
You dickheads were the ones cheating.
我们只是检举揭发了
We were just the whistleblowers.
就是啊 而且根本不是我干的
Yeah, and I didn't even do it.
好吗？是她啊
All right? It was her.
我大概是要为这事儿负责的
I am kind of responsible for that.
我知道 我本来就打算砸你的 跑偏了
I know. I meant to hit you, but my aim was off.
这不重要 从现在起
It doesn't matter. From now on,
你们谁都别想再踏进Theta兄弟会半步
none of you are ever setting foot in Theta again.
他把我橘子拿走了
He took my clementine.
我真抱歉发生了这样的事
I'm so sorry that happened to you.
嗯 我都习惯了 我跟我妈在各个剧院外面
Eh, I'm used to it. My mom and I have gotten
被扔了血袋
blood thrown on us outside multiple operas.
大家 我还是不敢相信我们不能再去Theta兄弟会的派对了
Guys, I can't believe we can't party at Theta anymore.
谁管他们啊？
Who cares about Theta?
他们都不能再办派对了
They can't even throw parties anymore.
我们再找个兄弟会一起玩就好了
We'll just find a new frat to hang with.
噢 我的天哪
Oh, my God.
-什么？-看啊
- What? - Look.
姑娘们 记得别在走廊上聚集
Girls, remember not to congregate in the hallways.
会有消防风险
It is a fire hazard.
这些老旧建筑就跟个火种盒一样 所以...
These old buildings are tinder boxes, so...
-谢谢 弗路德 -宿舍师友会上见
- Thanks, Frude. - See you at the FAF meeting.
欢迎回来 我的新生们
Welcome back, my Fresh-Them.
希望你们美国感恩节过得愉快
I hope you enjoyed American Thanksgiving,
你们没什么人转学真让我松了口气
and I'm relieved so few of you transferred.
我确实有好消息要告诉你们
I do have exciting news.
我们有个新成员
We have a new student joining us,
他是个气候难民
and he is climate refugee.
哇 我觉得能接收
Wow, I think it's great
背井离乡的人很棒诶
that we're taking in a displaced person.
是啊 他们是来自发展中国家吗
Yeah, are they from a developing nation?
不 他从堪萨斯州来的
No, he's from Kansas.
啊 现在他来了
Ah, here he is now.
大家 请给我们的气候难民
Everyone, please give a warm welcome
杰克逊一个热烈的欢迎
to our climate refugee, Jackson.
-大家好 -等等
- Hello. - Wait,
你就是那个气候难民？
you're the climate refugee?
-可你是白人诶 -贝拉
- You're white. - Bela.
-怎么了嘛？-亲爱的 嗯
- What the hell? - Sweetheart, um,
告诉大家发生了什么
tell us what happened to you,
还有你是不是直男啊 是单身吗
and if you're straight and single.
我真的不知道怎么去讲述这件事
I really don't know how else to say it.
我的大学宿舍被一阵四级龙卷风吹走了
My college dorm was blown away by a Category 4 tornado.
天哪
Shit.
-哇 -等等 你说什么？
- Wow. - Wait, what?
那太糟糕了 但是弗路德
That's terrible. But Frude,
我觉得“难民”这个词更多
I think the term "refugee" implies
指的是国际上的逃难
more of an international displacement.
嗯 金伯莉 别冒犯我的新朋友
Uh, Kimberly, do not offend my new friend.
他已经够不容易了
He's been through enough.
我觉得气候变化是真的
I think climate change is real.
-就是啊 你认真的吗？-我没说是假的啊
- Yeah, are you serious? - I didn't say it wasn't.
说起气候变化
And speaking of climate change,
天气预报说明天会下雪
tomorrow's forecast calls for snow,
这说明艾塞克斯最没有种族歧视的传统要来了
which brings with it Essex's oldest non-racist tradition,
年度雪季赛跑
The Annual Snow Run.
哦 我的天哪
Oh, my God!
是那个穿着内衣在雪里奔跑的活动吗？
Is that where we run in the snow in our underwear?
就是那个
That is correct.
我们要提前开始吗 还是等到开赛？
Should we pregame or wait till we get there?
哦 我们肯定要提前开始
Oh, we should absolutely pregame.
我们宿舍的酒可好太多了
The booze in our dorm is way better.
提醒一下 未成年喝酒是不合法的也不好玩
Reminder, underage drinking is illegal and not fun.
我们下一个吸引人的话题才真正好玩...
But what is fun is our next juicy topic...
避免季节性抑郁
Avoiding seasonal depression.
嘿 金伯莉
Hey, Kimberly.
嘿 你是不是给我买了个同性恋彩虹气球柱
Hey, did you buy me a column of gay pride balloons?
哦 我的天 我买了
Oh, my God. I did.
真对不起
I'm so sorry.
我以为你会在休息期间告诉惠特尼和贝拉
I assumed you told Whitney and Bela over break,
但是你没说 我也取消不了订单了
but then you didn't, and I couldn't cancel them.
有其他人看见吗？
Did anyone else see them?
我让你跟大家出柜了吗？我是个糟糕的盟友吗？
Have I outed you? Am I bad ally?
不 你没事的
No, you're fine.
我就是很困扰
I'm just disturbed that you think I am
你以为我是那种喜欢这些东西的同性恋
the kind of gay person who would like that.
了解 你和惠特尼和贝拉出柜的时候
Got it. When you come out to Whitney and Bela,
我会给你买个普通一定的气球塔
I'll get you a classier balloon tower.
我的出柜计划不包括气球啦
My ideal coming-out does not involve balloons.
完全不要 求你了
No balloons at all, please.
你要跟贝拉和惠特尼说吗？
Are you gonna tell Bela and Whitney?
也许有一天会 但不是现在
At some point, probably, but not right now.
好 我与你同在
Well, I'm here for you.
好的 我得去助学金办公室
Okay, I gotta go to the financial aid office
去申请贷款了
to ask for a loan.
祝我好运吧
Wish me luck.
等等 你打算穿着你工作制服去？
Wait, wearing your Sips uniform?
对啊 我想让他们知道我有工作
Yeah, I want them to know I have a job.
挺聪明的 对吧？
It's pretty smart, right?
金伯莉 银行只会把钱给看起来
Kimberly, banks only give money to people
本来就很有钱的人
who look like they already have money.
我来帮你
Let me help you.
-金伯莉·芬克尔？-这儿呢
- Kimberly Finkle? - Here.
我超期待比赛淡季的
I'm so psyched for the off-season.
我被足球打中好几次了
I got hit with a soccer ball so many times,
我都觉得我的乳头得了慢性脑创伤了
I think my titties got CTE.
那我们闲下来要做什么啊？
So what are we gonna do with all our free time?
我觉得可以一觉睡到三点
I'm thinking sleeping till 3:00
然后喝酒喝到下一个三点
and then drinking till the other 3:00.
嗯 那不适合我 我的行程可满了
Mm, that's a no for me. My schedule's packed.
已经满了？现在？
Already? How?
比赛淡季就是要做平时练习期间
Off-season is when we do all the stuff
所有我们不能做的事
we can't do during soccer.
我在竞选学生政府
I'm running for student government.
你看见这些失败者了吗？我得打败他们
Have you seen those losers? I'm gon' clean up.
你为什么竞选啊？
Why would you wanna do that?
宝贝 那是给毕业简历上增光添彩
Pad that grad school résumé, babe.
是啊 我已经有篮球项目了 我已经是两赛季的运动员了
Yeah, I've got basketball. I'm a two-season athlete.
但是你刚刚说睡觉喝酒
But you were just joking about sleeping
一整天都是开玩笑的对吧？
and drinking all day, right?
是啊 当然了 肯定是开玩笑的
Yes, duh, totally.
我有很多事要去做呢 咱走吧
I've got so much going on. Let's go.
这个 芬克尔小姐
Well, Ms. Finkle,
我们可以给你批贷款了
I think we're gonna be able to get you this loan.
哦 天哪 真的吗？ 真让人松了口气
Oh, my God, really? That's such a relief.
我乐意帮忙 你 嗯 有其他问题吗？
I'm happy to help. Do you, uh, have any questions?
-没有 -有问题的 其实
- No. - Actually, yes.
贷款什么时候开始积累利息
When does the loan start accruing interest,
利息是固定的还是变化的呢？
and is it fixed or variable?
好问题
Great questions.
我把这个手册给你好了
Let me just get you this pamphlet.
哦 哇
Oh, wow.
这上面每个人看起来都好开心哦
Everyone in here looks so happy.
金伯莉 这些人就是平面模特而已
Kimberly, they're print models.
我已经在一个节育环广告上看见过这个女生了
I've seen that girl in a NuvaRing ad.
你可以带我们再过一遍还款流程吗？
Can you at least walk us through the payback structure?
嗯 好的 根据你的贷款数目
Uh, well, with a loan your size,
未来三十年 每个月你要还款900刀
you'd be paying about $900 a month for the next 30 years.
不过有自动还款 你都不会意识到
But with autopay, it's like you don't even know
钱从你的账户上被划走了
the money's leaving your account.
你一直到 大概 五十岁才会把钱还完
You're gonna be paying this back until you're, like, 50.
哦 完成还款的平均年龄实际上会在你快七十岁的时候
Oh, the payoff age is actually late-60s on average.
我都没有别的选择
I don't have any other options.
我想要借这笔贷款
I'd like to go ahead with the loan.
好极了 让我们把钱给你吧
Wonderful, let's get you that shmoney.
我只要把纸质文件拿来
I'm just gonna go grab the paperwork
给你父母共同签署就行
for your parents to cosign.
不要！
No!
我是说 如果不能给我父母签呢
I mean, what if that's not an option?
很抱歉 但是有共同签署人这件事没得商量
I'm sorry, but a cosigner is kind of a non-negotiable.
哦 那我想我办不了贷款了
Oh, then I don't think I can do this.
谢谢你花时间招待
Thanks for your time.
欢迎各位来自艾塞克斯搞笑女们
Welcome, funny ladies of Essex.
我们很荣幸邀请到大家参加
We're so happy you're interested in joining
我们学校有史以来第一本全女性搞笑杂志
our school's first ever, female-only comedy magazine.
我知道你们在想什么
I know what you're thinking.
没有一些男人抄袭柯南秀和周六夜现场
Will it be hard to do this without a bunch of guys
的创意 这件事会不会很难办呢？
who steal all their ideas from Conan and "SNL"?
不 不会的
No, it will not.
只要你在这间屋子里
If you're in this room,
就意味着你已经是我们的一份子了...
it means you're part of the movement...
除了那个看起来像在写作业的家伙
Except for that guy, who's doing homework, I think.
我们还在努力找个永久会议室
We're still working on finding a permanent meeting space.
我们迫不及待要读你们的投稿了
We're so excited to read your submissions.
未来几天
In a few short days,
你们中将会产生幸运女孩来加入我们
some of you lucky ladies will be joining us
撰写我们开创性第一版
in writing our groundbreaking first edition
成为我们搞笑姐妹原始成员
as one of our newfound comedy sisters.
我的天 这些女孩完全是群无聊的狗屎
Holy shit, these girls are unfunny turds.
是好事？
In a good way?
这怎么会是好事啊？
How would that be in a good way?
贝拉 你反应过渡了
Bela, you're overreacting.
有些...还可以吧 你读过这些了吗？
Some are... fine. Have you read these?
这个女生写了一首跟腹腔疾病有关的诗
This girl wrote a poem about celiac disease,
这个女生写了一个叫“OBGY-LOL”的词组
and this girl wrote a phrase called "OBGY-LOL."
-这到底什么意思？-所以他们还有的要学呢
- What does that even mean? - So they have a lot to learn.
-我们可以教他们 -我真的希望他们能写出来
- We'll teach them. - I really need this to work.
我希望和搞笑的作者合作
I wanna write with writers that are funny,
像你跟乔一样
like you and Jo.
-还有我 -当然当然
- And me. - Sure.
听着 我们从一开始就不觉得能马上
Look, none of us thought we were gonna find
找到一大堆很不错又很搞笑的人
a bunch of amazing and hilarious people right away.
耐心点好吗？
Just be patient, okay?
好吧
Okay.
真遗憾你的助学贷款没申请下来 金伯莉
Sorry about your loan, Kimberly.
如果能让你高兴一点的话
If it makes you feel any better,
我的杂志这边也是一塌糊涂
my new comedy magazine's a disaster.
真的吗？为什么？
Really? Why?
因为她们超烂的
Because they all stink.
我猜《卡图兰》1994年以前不让女性
I'm worried "The Catullan" was onto something
加入肯定是有原因的
not letting women join until 1994.
听着 虽然我对
Look, I don't know anything
喜剧一点都不了解...-太对了
about comedy... - So true.
非常正确
So, so true.
但是也许你在做这些事之前
But maybe, before you throw this all away,
你应该找个之前这么干过的人聊聊
you should talk to someone who's done it before.
这听起来确实是个不错的主意
That does seem like good advice.
噢 这样的话 我有些不错的消息
Ooh, well, I have some cool news.
我打算加入水球队了
I'm gonna be on the water polo team.
-真的吗？-什么？
- Really? - What?
我都不知道你还会打水球呢
I didn't know you played water polo.
哦 我现在还不会...但是看起来挺简单的
Oh, I don't... yet. But it seems easy.
我看过水球视频
Based off a video I watched,
感觉就像在水里用手踢足球
I think it's just pool soccer with hands.
这样我们还可以跟
And then we can hang out
打水球的男生一起玩
with the water polo guys.
你知道吗 也许日子确实还是有盼头的
You know, maybe things are looking up.
噢 我的胸！
Ow, my boob!
他爹的怎么了？
What the fuck?
真对不起啊 不过不是真心的
Sorry. Not really, though.
现在这是垃圾了 你们这些垃圾
Now it's trash, you trash.
穿点衣服吧
Put your clothes on.
噢 操 我得给我的胸冰敷一下
Aw, fuck. I gotta ice my boob.
等等 这是什么？
Wait, what is that?
你们听见了吗？
Did you guys hear that?
噢我的天哪
Oh, my God.
做爱的声音！
Sex noises!
等等 是那个气候难民
Wait, that's the climate refugee.
是他的房间
That's his room.
想知道那个女生是谁
Wonder who she is.
这个 管她是谁 这可是她人生大事
Well, whoever she is, she's having the time of her life.
他们声儿也太大了
They are being so loud.
这就是噪音污染啊 我得敲敲门
It's literal noise pollution. I'm gonna knock.
你敢！
Don't you dare!
让我先录点下来
Just let me record a little first.
贝拉？现在是早上8:15分
Bela? It's 8:15 in the morning.
-你怎么会在这儿？-有急事儿
- Why are you here? - It's urgent.
你怎么找到我家的？
How did you find my apartment?
我故意不告诉你在哪的
It was a very conscious choice to not tell you where it was.
听着 我的新杂志一团糟
Look, my new magazine is a disaster.
所有投稿人都糟透了 所以我打算
All the applicants suck, which is why I've decided
马上就放弃 接受我之前在
to immediately give up and accept my old spot
《卡图兰》的工作 贝拉回来了
on "The Catullan." Bela's back.
不客气
You're welcome.
嗯 不要
Um, no.
没人想要跟一个离开还要带走
I don't think anyone's gonna be excited to work with a girl
我们得力战将对女生继续合作
who left and stole all of our good writers.
他们是自愿离开的 《卡兰图》糟透了
They left willingly. "The Catullan" sucked.
你刚还说想回来
You just said you wanted to come back to it.
那好吧 你愿意来我的杂志干吗？
Fine then. Will you join my magazine?
我要说什么你才能离开我家？
What can I say that will help you leave my apartment?
我该怎么办？
What do I do?
嗯 好吧
Um, okay,
你打算建立一个团队对吧？
so you're building a team, right?
你应该把这件事认为是你的勒布朗时刻
So you gotta look at this as your LeBron moment.
这是你组成一个超级搞笑团队的机会
This is your chance to put together a super comedy lineup.
对吧？就像 勒布朗不会等着人来
Right? Like, LeBron didn't just wait
加入队伍
for people to come join the team.
他走出去了 然后他找到了
He went out, and he found
德韦恩·韦德和克里斯·波什
Dwyane Wade and Chris Bosh.
哦哦 了解了
Uh-huh, got it.
你可以不用体育术语再解释一遍么？
Can you put that in not sports terms?
就是去找一堆搞笑的人
Just find a bunch of funny people.
好的
Cool.
早上好 女士们
Good morning, ladies.
欢迎来到水球能力考核
Welcome to water polo tryouts.
我们将分组比赛来评估你们的技能水平
We're gonna do a scrimmage so I can assess your skill level.
听起来挺有趣
This seems fun.
你之前玩过水球吗？
You ever played water polo before?
玩过 我打比赛八年了
Yup, I played competitively for eight years.
这样啊 我刚开始 但是我敢保证
Yeah, I just started, but I'm pretty sure
这项运动也会在我人生轨迹上了
it's gonna be my life now too.
哦 对了 我快速地问一下 规则是什么？
Ooh, also, real quick, what are the rules?
冲 冲 冲 冲 开始了！
Up, up, up, up! Let's go!
女孩们快来 快下水！
Come on, ladies! Get in the water!
就是这样 这就对了！
Here we go, yes!
好了 开始 传球！
All right, let's go. Pass it!
为什么你们的手臂不用来游泳？
How are you guys not using your arms to swim right now?
加油 你们能行的！
Come on, you got this!
我再问一下我是哪个对的来着？
Which team am I on again?
开始！快快快！
Let's go! Quickly!
我 让我接！我空着...
Me, I got it! I'm open...
传球！高点儿！
Transition! High!
我空着呢！我可以接...
I'm open! I'm ope...
你被打昏了 不过我给你做人工呼吸了
You got knocked out, but I gave you mouth-to-mouth.
谢谢了
Thanks.
我觉得我现在知道怎么玩了
I think I get the rules now.
我应该再回去打比赛吗？
Should I jump back in?
不用了
No.
-你的助学贷款怎么样了？-说实话不咋地
- So how'd it go with the loan? - Honestly, not great.
他们说我得找我父母共同签署贷款
They said they need my parents to cosign my loan,
我也不能告诉他们发生了什么
and I can't tell them what happened.
-那你打算怎么办？-噢 我有个主意
- So what are you gonna do? - Ooh, I have an idea.
我表妹被公交车撞了之后赔了不少钱
My cousin got a bunch of money when she was hit by a city bus.
你也去撞一下 -事实上 我
Do that. - Actually, I found
另外一个超高薪的工作 可以在宿舍做的
a super high-paying second job I can do from my dorm room.
我给一个名叫《性爱天堂：澳大利亚》
I'm typing up the closed captioning
的真人秀打上字母
for a reality show called "Sex Paradise: Australia."
-这也叫工作？-当然啊
- That's a job? - It sure is.
我要做的就是看一集
All I have to do is watch an episode,
仔细听 然后把他们说的话
listen very closely, and type up what they're saying...
还有他们在欢乐小屋里弄出的噪音打到字幕上就行
And the noises they make in the Pleasure Hut...
他爹的二十块一个小时呢 -好恶心啊
For 20 freakin' bucks an hour. - That's disgusting.
他们要付你几集的钱啊？
How many episodes are they paying you for?
一季三百集
It's 300 episodes a season.
如果我一个星期能找到至少
So if I can find time to transcribe
五十个小时去打字幕 加上我在学校的工作和
for at least 50 hours a week, on top of my school work
在这里的工作 我的经济问题就完美解决了
and my Sips job, my finances will be totally taken care of.
那时间也太长了
That's too much.
你应该直接把事儿跟你妈说了
You should just tell your mom what happened
然后让她跟你一起签贷款合同
and have her cosign a loan.
不要 我打算按我的计划行事
No, I'm gonna go with my thing.
好吧
Okay.
我也没有别的兴趣了
I don't have any other interests.
这样 你说什么才是我的王牌 除了足球？
Okay, what would you say is my thing, besides soccer?
你很酷
That you're cool.
你很漂亮
And you're pretty.
你可以唱卡拉OK 但是唱的一般
And you can kind of sing karaoke, but not really.
说真的 迦南
Seriously, Canaan.
我都不知道发生了什么
I don't get what's going on.
我想我有点迷茫
I guess I'm feeling... lost.
好吧 这样的话 你以后想做什么过活？
Okay, well, what do you wanna do with your life?
我不知道 你呢？
I don't know. What about you?
事实上 我有个非常详细的十年计划
Well, I actually have a very detailed ten-year plan
引领我建立自己的避险基金
that will hopefully lead me into starting my own hedge fund
用来帮助巨额投资的
that focuses on impact investing.
所以我基本上相当于在帮人的同时
So I'll basically be helping people
变得越来越富有
while getting very, very rich.
这就是我要说的啊
That's exactly what I'm talking about.
我感觉我是大学里唯一一个
I feel like I'm the only person in college
不知道自己的未来何去何从的人
who doesn't have their whole life already figured out.
感觉挺糟糕的
It kind of sucks.
这个嘛 我知道你迟早会弄清楚的
Well, I know you're gonna figure it out,
因为你很聪明啊 而且不管你用心做什么
because you're smart, and whatever you put your mind to,
你都会成功拿下的
you're gonna kill it.
-谢谢你 -除了玩水球
- Thank you. - Unless it's water polo.
我就知道你要这么说
I knew you were gonna do that.
哦 我的天 你们大家
Oh, my God, you guys.
好 现在已经有这么多雪了
Okay, there is so much snow already.
这真的安全吗？
Are we sure this is safe?
像是 我们的胸会被冻伤吗？
Like, do people get boob frostbite?
我想应该不会吧 但是值得查一下
I don't think so, but it's definitely worth a Google.
行了 既然这个雪中赛跑终点在兄弟会大街
Okay, so the snow run ends at Frat Row,
所有的兄弟会都会在那办大派对
where all the frats will be hosting big parties,
既然Theta出局了
and since Theta's out,
我做了详细的Instagram追踪
I did some comprehensive Instagram stalking
来找出下一个最佳选项
to figure out the next best option,
就决定是Omega Pi了
and it is definitely Omega Pi.
不管谁去看都知道他们
Their guys are for sure the hottest
的成员是最帅的 -这就是我
if anyone wants to check. - Is that why
打印机没墨的原因吗？-都2022年了
my printer is out of ink? - It's 2022.
你为什么还有个打印机？这都怪你
Why do you even have a printer? This is on you.
我刚刚说的 Omega Pi将要举办
As I was saying, Omega Pi's hosting
一个盛大的冬季陆上派对
a huge Winter Under land party.
这会是个公开活动 我们都要去
It is gonna be lit, and we're all going.
我不去了 我得在家做我的打字幕工作
Not me. I have to stay home and do some closed captioning.
-你确定吗？-是啊
- Are you sure? - Yeah.
我觉得这近期都是我的常态了
I think this is gonna be my new normal for a while.
好吧 姐妹们 我们几个去
All right. We gotta go, ladies.
好的 好的 等等等 我能说
Okay, okay, wait, wait, wait. Can I just say
我们三个现在看起来都太他爹的性感了吗
that all three of us look so fucking hot right now
这会是我们人生中最棒的一天
and that this is gonna be one of the best days of our lives!
哦 我的天哪！
Oh, my God!
啊 我的 喔 喔！
Ah, my-ow, ow!
贝拉 贝拉 停下 停下
Bela, Bela, stop, stop.
起来！起来！
Get up! Get up!
杰西卡刚刚
Jessica has just made
做了一个残忍的决定
the bloody agonizing decision
她要甩了布莱克斯顿
to dump Braxton,
现在她要自己面对后果
and now she deals with the consequences.
你知道 这是 就像 一个游戏 对吗？
You know, it's, like, a game, right?
但是这也是 像是 寻找真爱 你知道吗？
But it's also, like, finding love, you know?
她他爹的到底在说什么？
What the fuck is she saying?
她要甩了布莱克斯顿
To dump Braxton,
现在她要自己面对后果
and now she deals with the consequences.
你知道 这是 就像 一个游戏 对吗？
You know, it's, like, a game, right?
但是这也是 像是 寻找真爱 你知道吗？
But it's also, like, finding love, you know?
真操蛋
God damn it.
你们能不能小声点？
Can you please keep it down?
闭嘴！
Shut up!
混蛋！
Assholes!
大家 都干了！两分钟之后开赛！
Everyone, drink up! We run in two minutes!
我眼球都冷了
My eyeballs are cold.
-对啊 -嗯 我也是
- Yeah. - Uh, same.
嘿！
Hey!
-你怎么在这儿！-金伯莉！
- You're here! - Kimberly!
什么...我还以为你要工作呢
What... I thought you had to work.
我觉得我干不来这活儿
I don't think I can do that job.
喝醉的澳大利亚人说话太难懂了
Drunk Australian people are so hard to understand,
尤其是在我们邻居做爱还这么大声的时候
especially with our neighbor having sex so loud.
这个嘛 你也不需要今晚解决所有问题
Well, you don't have to fix all your problems tonight,
但是有一件事你必须做
but there is one thing you do have to do.
确实是 脱掉你的外套
Exactly. Take off that coat.
让我们看看你的老奶奶内裤
Let me see those granny panties.
天哪
God damn,
原来过时衣服下的你这么性感
underneath all those unstylish clothes, you're, like, hot.
哦 那当然了
Oh, hell yeah,
姑娘 恭喜你穿内衣光彩夺目
congrats on the underwear glow-up, girl.
大家准备好开跑了吗？
Everybody ready to run?
三 二 一
Three, two, one,
脱掉外套开跑！
strip and go!
动一动啊 你这家伙！我很快的！
Move, bitch! I'm fast!
-嘿 -真不错
- Hey. - Yeah.
去他的Theta Omega Pi才是我们该来的地方
Fuck Theta. Omega Pi is where it's at.
我从来没有在同一个地方看见过这么多
I have never seen this many hot,
不穿衣服的帅哥
shirtless men in one place.
就是啊 我疯狂用眼睛截图
I know. I'm taking screenshots
待会儿再在脑海里欣赏
but with my brain for later.
我也一样 不过我还在手机里拍了些照片
Same, except I also tooka couple pictures on my phone.
哦 你看见那边的顺直大肌霸了吗？
Oh, see that pack of cis daddies right there?
我可以清晰地看见他们每个人的鸡巴形状
I can see every single one of their dick shapes.
那边的老兄 他的四角短裤里
Homie on the right got a big ol' toddler arm
可有根像小孩手臂这么粗的
in his boxer briefs.
-莱拉？-嗯？
- Lila? - Hmm?
你有没有兴趣为我的搞笑杂志写一篇
Would you ever be interested in writing a listicle
关于鸡巴形状的清单体文章？
about dick shapes for my comedy magazine?
这个 虽然我不知道清单体他爹的是个什么东西
Well, I don't know what the fuck a listicle is,
但是 妞儿 我当然愿意 让我们开写
but hell yes, bitch, let's do it.
嘿 我是萨拉
Hey, I'm Sara.
嘿 我是金伯莉 这是蕾登
Hey, I'm Kimberly. This is Leighton.
知道了 你想跳舞吗？
Cool. You wanna dance?
这个 我现在正和我朋友跳舞呢
Um, I'm actually just dancing with my friend right now.
好吧
Okay.
我本来打算要去厕所
I was actually gonna go to the bathroom,
所以我现在要去上厕所了
so I'm gonna go do that.
那么 嗯 想喝一杯吗？
So, uh, you want a shot?
闻着味道就知道 这肯定是非常差的龙舌兰酒
From the smell of it, I'd say it's shockingly bad tequila.
嗯 那真糟糕啊
Mm, horrible.
行啊 我来一杯
Yeah, I'm down.
不 我给你倒
No, let me do it for you.
张嘴
Open your mouth.
嗯 事实上 我可以的 我自己来
Um, actually, I'm good. I'm good.
嗯 抱歉 但是我只喝好酒
Um, sorry, but I only drink top shelf.
行吧
All right.
谢谢
Thanks.
-我的胸掉出来了吗？-没啊 没掉出来
- Are my boobs poppin' out? - No, you're good.
我正打算让微醺滑步成为我的标志性舞步呢
I'm trying to make on-purpose nip slips my signature move.
哦 那他爹的气候难民在这儿呢
Oh, that fucking climate refugee is here.
我的天 你看他拿着啤酒的样子
Holy shit. Look at him holding that beer.
他的手臂真的不得了
Dude has Marvel arms.
是啊 对 现在我有点知道
Yeah. Yeah, now I kind of get
为什么那个女孩叫这么大声了
why that girl was being so loud.
-你好 你是杰克逊 对吗？-对啊
- Hi. It's Jackson, right? - Yeah.
是这样 我是金伯莉 我住在你隔壁
Well, I'm Kimberly. My room is right next to yours.
-挺好的 -事实上不怎么好
- Cool. - It's actually not cool,
因为你才刚来艾塞克斯大概三天
because you've been at Essex for, like, three days,
你就已经完成了世界上最大声
and you're already having the loudest,
最有表现力的性爱
most performative sex in the world.
提醒你一下 这个学校里还有一些人
For your information, some of the people at this school
有真正的要紧事要做呢
have some really important work to do,
当你想让你自己不去听
and that's hard when you're,
墙对面的哼哼声的时候
you know, grunting your head off going like...
认真做事是很困难的
On the other side of some very,
墙非常薄 好吗？
very, thin drywall, okay?
-你说完了吗？-是的 我应该都说完了
- You done? - Yeah, I think so.
那个 你也知道 跟你们共用一堵墙
Well, just so you know, it actually kind of sucks
我也觉得挺糟糕的
sharing a wall with you too.
你最近看什么垃圾电视剧
What the hell ass TV show
看的这么大声
have you been watching so loudly?
那个是《性爱天堂：澳大利亚》
It's called "Sex Paradise: Australia."
我都不知道你还能听见这个
I didn't know you could hear it.
哦 我能听见的
Oh, I can.
让我看下你的手机
Let me see your phone.
我这个月流量已经用完了
I've already hit my data cap for the month,
别打开YouTube
so don't go on YouTube.
给你 现在你有我电话了
Here. Now you have my number.
要是我那边再有很吵的声音发出来
Just shoot me a text
你就给我发个短信
if anything on my side of the wall gets too loud.
-耶！-啊 不错啊 姑娘！
- Yeah! - Ah, yes, bitch!
我不知道啊 兄弟
I don't know, man.
关键是她除了足球真的啥也不会了
Thing is, she really doesn't have anything besides soccer,
所以我当时真的不知道说什么你知道吧？
so I didn't really know what to say, you know?
嘭！加油啊 我赢了
Boom! Let's go. That's mine.
这把我赢 滚回来 把球滚回来
That's all me. Run it back, run it back.
嘿 你还好吗？
Hey. You good?
嗯 我当然还好啦
Yeah. Course I am.
我刚刚吐在一个奖杯里了
I just threw up in a trophy.
谁还想再喝一杯？
Who wants another shot?
嘿 哇 哇 你在这儿喝的也太醉了
Hey, whoa, whoa, you are way too wasted to be here.
我该带你回家了
I think I gotta take you home.
不 不 不...
No, no, no...
-我等下给你发短信 -嗯嗯
- I'm gonna text you later. - Uh-huh.
说再见 冠军 该走了
Say goodbye, champ. It's time to go.
该走啦 呃 尝起来跟有人吐
Time to go. Ugh, it tastes like
在我嘴里一样
someone puked in my mouth!
你们今晚玩得开心吗？
Did you guys have fun tonight?
嗯 很开心！谢谢你的关心！
Yeah, we did! Thanks for asking!
不错
Great,
因为这是你们能去的最后一个派对了
because it'll be the last party you'll ever go to.
-老兄 你什么毛病啊？-说真的
- Dude, what is your problem? - Seriously.
是谁死了吗还让你管所有兄弟会？
Who died and made you king of all the frats?
你是个Theta成员
You're a Theta.
这些就是我跟你说过的女孩
These are the girls I was telling you about,
告我们密的人
the ones who narced on us.
你们是惹事精 姐们
You're a liability, bro.
惹事精？我们明明更惹人喜欢
A liability? More like like-ability.
有我们在身边可有意思了
We're a damn pleasure to have around.
-你们说是不是？-对啊
- Isn't that right? - Mm-hmm.
你们都他爹的滚出去
Y'all need to get the fuck out.
-哦 我的天哪 -我们会死的
- Oh, my God. - We're gonna die.
-我的乳头要冻伤了 -操蛋
- I'm getting nipple frostbite. - Fuck.
昨晚除了我们被禁止进入兄弟会
Barring the fact that we got banned from frats last night,
我还是觉得玩的挺开心的
I still think we had a really fun time.
金伯莉有了那个气候难民的电话号码
Kimberly got climate refugee's phone number.
为了紧急事件
For emergencies.
那你呢 蕾登 你有跟帅哥搭讪吗？
What about you, Leighton, did you chat up any hotties?
行吧 你太优秀了让人难以亲近
Fine. You're too classy to kiss and tell.
我都懂的
I get it.
呃 实际上 我本来打算跟
Uh, actually, there is something
你们说一些事的
that I've been meaning to tell you guys.
我是弯的
I'm gay.
哇 蕾登 太酷了吧
Wow, Leighton, that's awesome.
我们应该报一下吗 我感觉我们应该拥抱一下
Should we hug? I feel like we should hug.
呃 不用 我们不需要 我们不需要拥抱
Uh, no, we don't... We don't need to hug.
哦 蕾登 这也太酷了 我 我也很震惊
Oh, Leighton, that's so cool. And I-I'm so shocked.
我是说 我不知道 我猜我的
I mean, I had no idea. I guess it's like
姬达可能失效了
my gaydar is way off or something.
金伯莉早就知道了 对吧？
Kimberly already knew, didn't she?
但她在这件事上真的是个好朋友
She's been a really good friend about it, though.
她昨晚在派对上甚至试着让我单独
She even tried to get me alone
和一个女孩儿待在一块儿
with a girl at the party last night.
哦 我的天哪 我看见跟你们说话的那个女孩了
Oh, my God, the girl I saw you talking to.
她超性感的
She was so hot.
是啊
Yeah.
是啊 但是后来...后来我 就像是 害怕极了 然后表现得很奇怪
Yeah, but then... then I, like, freaked out and got weird,
她应该对我再也不感兴趣了 所以...
and she's probably not interested anymore, so...
不可能 如果你现在给她发消息
No way. If you DM'd her right now,
我保证事情还是有回转的余地的
I promise you it would be back on.
滑到她的页面
Slide into her DM.
-对啊 给她发消息 -现在 快发
- Yeah, message her. - Now, do it.
发消息 发消息
Slide in, slide in.
行吧 好吧 好吧 我会发的
All right, fine. Fine, I'll do it.
我就发个“你好”
I said, "Hi."
对！
Yes!
你怎么进来的？
How are you in here?
我都让他们改密码了
I literally had them change the buzzer code.
我等别人出去再进来的
I waited for someone to exit.
我就是想跟你说声谢谢
I just wanted to say thank you
谢谢你的建议
for your advice.
我找到了一个超搞笑的作者
I found another super funny writer
是个我觉得很棒的人
who I think is gonna be great,
你真的帮了我的忙
so it really helped.
你早上7:45来这里就是为了说这些？
You came here at 7:45 just for that?
对啊 就这些
Yeah, just that.
去睡觉吧
Go to bed.